As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices We take in the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled
yeah yeah Here we are
in between the sea and
the sky Ready now for adventure We're itching
to try Get ready to roam So all aboard
now we're set to go Set sail to the ocean
so deep Ready for a truly grand adventure
Well don't you think that sounds really
fun All this excitement is second to none
As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled
If there's something that I just won't ever
forget It's the way that I felt when our
journey was set Now I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you now, fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
You want already oh yeah
i'm here because of that
crap you pulled earlier
when you took my shadow.
With that lamp i'm taking it back
along with Serious sanjis and brooks.
Oh and the old zombie guys too.
All of them.
Ah you're greedy one aren't you and
how do you plan on achieving all that.
Obviously by kicking your ass. Oh.
You say you're gonna kick
my ass yep that's right.
Well even if you do manage to beat me
or Even kill me it won't do any good.
The zombies will lose their master
but the shadows won't Return to you.
Oh yeah that's right my power
controls the shadows that's absolute.
So fair warning if you
want the shadows back then
there's only one solution you
have to get the commander.
The shadows and other words
need to issue them an order
because they aren't going
anywhere unless i Say so.
And that's all it's gonna
take to get them back.
You got it pretty simple huh.
You might even Be able to force me to
return them if you kick my ass hard enough.
Well i say that but with your power.
I doubt you can even lay a finger on me.
All right, then.
Gum-Gum!
Pistol!
A shadow?
You have to go through him first.
Consider him my double.
I call him the Doppelman.
In the past, I was just like you,
overconfident in my abilities
and full of unrealistic ambition.
But then I realized the key to victory
is having underlings, real strong ones.
You suck, Doppelguy! Come on! Move it!
I'll never do anything on my own again.
Without lifting a finger, my minions
will make me the king of the pirates!
The king of the pirates is going to be me!
I seem to recall your zombie
making the same claim.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
When there's such an extreme difference
between the body and the shadow,
then the personality of the shadow's
original owner lingers a bit more than usual.
But that sort of thing can't
last forever, you know.
It's only a matter of time before
all your memories will fade,
and Oz becomes an obedient zombie
slave just like the others.
No matter how strong its will may be, every
zombie will bounce me sooner or later.
I don't mind being patient for a while.
I'll get my shadow back first!
Come, come!
Come, Brickbat!
Get me!
Damn, these things keep blocking me.
How am I supposed to punch him?
Don't worry, kid.
They don't actually drink blood.
To think you defeating me? Ridiculous.
Not dead now!
Rookie pirate, so cocky.
You fools are just setting yourselves
up for your own humiliation.
Bastard!
You've really pissed me off!
Come, Gunk!
He jumped.
Is he trying to escape? What a coward.
Snap!
Ah, you brat!
What a tip-shot!
Your ass just got kicked!
How about that?
Why is that a Nami I see?
Get your hands off her!
Oh, sorry to keep you waiting.
The night has arrived!
Wait, this is a goddess?
No, wait a sec.
I got confused.
This is definitely Nami.
Just calm down man. That's crazy.
What a surprise It's just she was so
beautiful I mean, princesses are nice and all.
What the hell is he mumbling about?
This moron is out of his mind.
Hey, you're a member of that
pirate crew, aren't you?
It's an angel.
No, no, it's just my bride. My mistake.
That scared me.
I know, right?
I feel you on that one, man.
I mean, it's like the only things that
look good in white or Nami and rice.
Amen, brother
You might say one look at her
will stop you white in your tracks
Enough chitchat.
Don't you try to get friendly with me
Hey
You almost hit Nami with that!
Attacking me is one thing, but show some
damn courtesy when there's a lady around!
Oh, by the way, your
shadow—it's gone, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
One of the new zombies we created
was strangely attached to my bride.
It seems the will of his shadow hadn't
faded, so he wasn't obedient to us just yet.
You won't lay a hand on this lady!
That must have been your zombie.
How pathetic!
They didn't even bother
putting your shadow
in a zombie general and
since that's the case,
I'm assuming your fighting
skills are pretty weak.
Both of you are overdressed, weaklings
that run your mouth too much.
I am one of the mysterious three.
All of the zombie generals
are under my command.
Do you really think you
stand a chance against me?
Who is that?
Oh,
it's Nami again.
This is really messing me up.
Actually, you know what—I'll be generous.
If you drag your sorry,
shadowless carcass out of here right now
and never come back, I'll let you go.
The thing is, I'm really busy right now.
Your stupid captain, stupid zombie,
went on a rampage and smashed
up some of my best men.
But before I deal with that, I'm
kissing my damn bride—and that's final!
You follow me.
I'm running very low on patience.
I can't waste my time fighting
with something like you.
Say, I talked too much.
You, creeper master Anselm?
No way—he weighs more than 600 pounds
and he got knocked back just like that.
So this is the big bad
invisible man Usopp was talking.
man Usopp was talking
about.
What was with that kick?
Hawkback made my body
into the perfect animal.
No human should
be able to do that to me.
Hands of the dead!
How did he know what I was going to do?
Damn it, Who is this guy?
I don't know!
You're the guy that showed up on the sunny
and dragged your filthy
tongue all over Robin,
aren't you?
Something is grabbing me.
And I heard you were peeping on Nami
while she was naked in the bath, too!
Hush, my darling.
El Drone! Plaché! Halcini!
This guy is just a nobody.
How is he so strong?
Koza!
Jode!
Why the hell is Nami unconscious, huh?
You better not have done
anything weird to her.
You call this crap a wedding?
You say that to my face again and I'll
pound you into a croquette, you hear me?
I think I'd better pull back for a second.
Invisiscuity.
Time for Usopp's salt balls.
There you are.
What is this, salt?
What's going on you say you're
running low on patience?
Well I'm way beyond that buddy!
I'm so pissed off I'm about to explode!
And this isn't just about
Nami either. Oh, no,
there's an issue a
little something between
the two of us that goes back a long way
He knocked him flat all right.
Let's talk about this.
You said there's an issue.
Damn straight.
For starters, you're a thief.
You stole Nami and you stole my dream.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You've got me confused with someone else.
We've never even met.
Before but if you want
to pick a fight with me,
we'll start with my hands of the dead.
Come on.
I 'LL BLOW YOU AWAY!
The guns. Take them off.
Don't play dumb.
Take off those bazookas you've
got strapped to your arms.
I'll only say this once.
If Nami gets injured in your crossfire,
by the time I'm done with you,?
you'll be twice as dead
as those zombies of yours.
Impossible.
How could he have known?
I tried asking you nicely.
Now take those damn things off!
What the? Bazookas?
Where did those even come from?
I figured it was something like that.
A guy with your powers only got
so many tricks up his sleeve.
I know you can turn invisible.
And I know you can turn
anything you touch invisible to.
but that's the extent of your powers.
Against me, your tactics are as
transparent as you are.
Because I know everything
about the clear clear fruit.
Who the hell are you?
Who told you that?
This guy, do you think he and Absalom
have got some kind of history?
That's the only thing
that makes any sense.
I scoured the Devil Fruit
encyclopedia when I was a kid.
I didn't even believe half
of it and most of the fruits
abilities didn't sound like they
were worth the curse anyway,
except for one.
There was one fruit that spoke to my
very soul, and I made the decision,
if I ever had the luck
of finding that fruit,
then I would embrace the curse and
swallow it whole no matter what the cost.
But of course, there's only
one of each Devil Fruit in the
entire world.
So I knew that if I ever met the
power holder with that ability,
my dream would be Vanquished
see what you've done the only
thing I wanted was to experience
invisibility for myself.
But you just had to go and find the
clear clear fruit first you took
its powers and you stole my dream
along with it that's why he's mad
my dream I saw it so clearly I
could do so much good with it use it
to protect new girls no I mean I
could help all mankind and new girls
no I had this beautiful vision of
the future and no girls he just
wants to peek at naked girls he's
a complete pervert shut up after a
lifetime of fantasizing about that
fruit I know how much you can peep
no wait I mean I know how much you
can help humanity with it understand
not only did you kidnap
nami and endanger her life
but you've squandered
all the good I could have
done for this world no girls
no I meant wrath prepare
to suffer my wrath so
that's the issue here you're
mad I ate the clear clear
fruit before you could
find it you know that's
the most petty damn thing I
ever heard that's the word
petty you are a jealous
pervert you have no right
You can't call me that!
It takes one to know it!
You're right!
They're the same!
The exact same!
I'm done listening to this nonsense!
You're taking out your anger on the wrong
guy, and now I'm gonna give it back!
I don't just have the jaw of
a lion I got elephant skin
and 600 pounds of muscle
from bears and gorillas Dr.
Hawkback built this body
from the most Savage beasts
you could imagine it's a
savage patchwork quilt of
ferocity a Masterpiece the
clear clear fruit you crave
so much it's just a bonus
yet I've got another weapon,
just a tool to enhance
my strength. Understand?
So what?
You still paint!
He's got a pretty good point there!
No mere human could keep
kicking me like this.
My body would shatter
the bones in his legs.
But he keeps on attacking me
like I'm a bag of feathers.
But still, the last laugh will be mine.
You wanted this Devil Fruit power of mine,
and you want to steal
my future bride from me.
But face the facts, they're both mine.
The next thing I'm taking
from you is your life.
Back there,
once he grabbed Nami, she disappeared too,
and we weren't able to chase after him.
So you're coming after Nami, huh?
Well, you're not getting her.
What are you even looking for I'm invisible
moron but you can still feel my power
Oh really you think you can
save her by sacrificing yourself
Well that's fine with me
let's see how it works out
for you mystery manhandler
MISSING LAND KICK HER!
Put her down gently now!
Before you drop dead!
I'm so sorry, Nami!
You dropped her guess?
You don't care so much
about her after all.
Forgive me, Nami.
I don't want to ruin your
white dress with blood.
That damn coward using his
cheap powers to hide from me!
At least now I know the
reality behind my dream.
I'm glad!
Glad I didn't find that
damn Devil Fruit after all?
I can peep fine the way I am.
He's gonna peep after all!
Let go of me, damn it!
Let go!
I've got you now, you bastard.
With all the different animals
you've got stitched into you,
you're gonna make one
damn tasty casserole.
I said let go of my life!
Don't get cocky with me!
Extra chance!
That's a lot!
Nude girls, no.
You wanted to get married?
I now pronounce you man in war.
He won't stop chasing me!
If I could just figure
out how to finish him off,
I could get rid of all the other pirates!
Damn that long-nosed jerk!
He won't stop chasing me.
If I could just figure
out how to finish him off,
I could get rid of that snotty ghost girl.
Damn that zombie bear!
Stop running!
Quit chasing me and quit
running, ghost girl!
Quit chasing me!
Hurry up and take care
of him already, Koobasie!
Don't rock him!
Quit harassing my mister!
You're scaring her!
Stop it! Go away!
I'm coming for sure!
What kind of sick monster would
make such a violent teddy bear?
Come on. Special attack!
Flame ball!
It worked! It worked!
You're just like the
other zombies after all!
Now let's add a dash of
oil for a little entree
I like to call don't
cross this line technique!
What the?
Come and get me now, you stupid bear!
I'm brilliant!
I'm total genius!
And now that you're out of the equation,
your precious mistress kooky
laughter ghost girl is going down!
All right then it's time to
teach that ghost girl a lesson.
Yep a lesson in complete and total defeat.
What the she was right here
looking for me right this way.
Is this some kind of trick where is she
did she go outside no that can't be right.
This tower's so high
that she'd have to be.
What?
How in the hell are
you floating like that?
I thought your power was to control
ghosts Okay, before we go any further,
I should ask, what is your power?
That's my little secret, no
one messes with the princess.
Oh, and by the way, I
know how to beat you now!
And when I'm through with
you, your friends are next.
They won't have a chance in the world?
Oh, come on!
What the hell?
And everything was going so good!